[Music]
hey guys we have a few announcements of
things were really excited about but
before we get to that I think we have to
address the elephant in the room and if
you think this is bad just wait one
second spell very sorry about this yeah
so the reason we have mustaches is
because you've been doing a campaign for
Movember to help raise money to for the
Prevention of male suicide which is an
issue close to our hearts so we had the
kind of culmination of it yesterday our
Christmas party which was also designed
to celebrate hitting a hundred thousand
subscribers which we'll talk about and
the kind of set piece in it it was an
evening full of loads of people who've
collaborated with before we had DJs we
had music and then we the culmination
was David getting shaved live actually
in stages so there were mutton chops
there was a kind of Civil War era like
no hair on the chin but everything else
linked up that was my personal favorite
I think
and then finally ending up with the
mustache so that sort of explains why
this is happening so one of the reasons
for the party was hitting a hundred
thousand YouTube subscribers which we
managed on Tuesday and want to thank all
the subscribers for that and in
particular and members and we made a
little animation to say thank you which
we're gonna roll now
[Music]
so the members of the reason that we're
able to keep making the films and also
developed into a really good community
around the the kind of subjects that
we're covering on the channel so if you
are a viewer and you would like to
support us please do become a member so
we also wanted to update everybody on
what we have coming up not just on the
channel but also in our live events so
we have at the end of February a new
two-day event coming up a call which
we're calling impossible conversations
and it's sort of an extension of what we
started with our experimental collective
intelligence lab and it's it's a weekend
of really skilling up and levelling up
in what we need in order to be able to
have really difficult cultural
conversations because some great
facilitators coming in and it's really
around getting a tool kit so that
everything from understanding our
nervous systems to being able to corral
our breath to be able to understand what
are our core values that are playing out
or you have these conversations so
really looking forward to that and then
we're gonna do a bigger announcement
around this soon but we have our largest
event ever which is the rebel wisdom
festival which is a two-day festival of
ideas and embodiment indoors it's in
London that's gonna be the end of May
and will announce a little bit more
about that soon but we're very excited
about that as well and on the channel
we've got a whole series of films coming
up we've got films with John Vevey key
we've got a sequel to the war on sense
making peace with Daniel SHM Acton
Berger called war on sense making - and
we have an interview with Diane musho
Hamilton which I'm really excited about
that was a really good interview and
we've got a whole series of films world
with Jamie Weil who was over in London
recently and we also want to announce
that we have a new rebel wisdom
correspondent in Toronto who is Peter
Lindbergh who runs the intellectual
Explorers Club there and has been doing
some really really interesting work so
we've got a couple of films coming out
with him and I'm gonna play a little
clip from him now as a kind of
introduction it was something
interesting about the frame
the group intellectual explorers club
because it attracted invited all sorts
of different people with different
ideologies from M&S to men's rights
activists to conservatives liberals
and I was the facilitator taking in all
these points of views and just feeling
the tension of people waiting for their
turn so they can spit out their position
and I think this afforded me an
understanding and a visceral level of
the culture war because I got a
front-row seat to it and the unique
thing about the intellectual explores
club that I think you David witnessed
when you were here in Toronto is that
it's sort of like the Switzerland of the
culture war in the sense that it can
house all these nomadic tribes whether
it's the the rationalist or post
rationalists extinction rebellion
effective altruists feminists no men's
right activists they have a home there
and they don't feel threatened because
the frame of it is that we're
understanding them on their own terms
and the way I like to think of it that
Ken Wilber to reference his
developmental model or spiral dynamics
is that you know there's a certain
developmental stage where there's a
pre-modern there's a modern a postmodern
and if ken wilber is correct there is
sort of a pathological version of
post-modernism right now so I view this
performative agnosticism this
intellectual Explorers Club as gesturing
towards a healthy post-modernism having
the capability of just talking to
someone on their own terms
and it really leans on the omega Rule
what is the signal there that people are
giving you you can see the video from
the event the Peter and I did together
in Toronto in the members area of the
rebel wisdom website thank you for
watching thank you for subscribing and
let's get up to a million by the end of
the week you've got a massage I don't
keep forgetting you full of my style
getting rid of it a thing they get home
tonight
rebel wisdom is a new sense making
platform bringing together the most
rebellious and inspiring thinkers from
around the world if you're enjoying our
content then you can help us make more
by becoming a subscriber which will give
you access to a load of exclusive films
also you can then join our group zoom
cause to discuss the ideas in the films
and you can send us ideas for questions
for upcoming interviews and if you're a
regular viewer you'll know we talk a lot
about the value of embodying or actually
living out the ideas that we've talked
about so that's why we run regular
events in London check out the links on
the website for more and hope to see you
soon
you